ransquawk.com 2019-05-15

# RANsquawk

At RANsquawk we are committed to ensuring the privacy of our customers. This privacy policy explains RANsquawk’s privacy practices, including those of our Website located at www.ransquawk..com (“Site”), for our customers who purchase our products and services. The Site is owned and operated by The JET Group Ltd. By using our Site and services, you consent to the terms of this privacy policy 

  1. ## What is Personal Information?

Personal information is information that specifically identifies an individual such as a customer’s name, address, telephone number, e–mail address, credit card or other account number, and information about that individual’s activities when directly linked to that person, such as information about his or her purchases. Personal information also includes demographic information such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you. 

Personal information does not include “aggregate” information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of products, services or customers, from which individual customer identities have been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Likewise, information about the products you purchase may be collected and combined with information about the products purchased by others. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new products and services, and tailor existing products and services to customer desires. 

  2. ## What information do we collect and when?

You provide personal information to us in a number of ways when you visit our Site or use our service. For example, you provide us with personal information when you: 

    1. purchase products and services
    2. create a user account
    3. sign up for our email list or electronic newsletters
    4. participate in surveys
    5. elect to share content from our website(s) with your friends
    6. contact us by email for any reason (such as to request customer service or provide us with your comments/feedback). 
    7. fill out contact forms
    8. use our online chat service
    9. apply for a job with us

We collect your name, billing address, service usage address, email address, phone number, credit card information, login information, order information and payment settings in this manner. We also collect information about the device and browser you use, your network connection and your IP address. 

  3. ## How We Use Personal Information

RANsquawk uses your personal data: 

    * to provide goods and services to you;
    * to make a tailored website available to you;
    * to manage any registered account(s) that you hold with us;
    * to verify your identity;
    * for crime and fraud prevention, detection and related purposes;
    * with your agreement, to contact you electronically about promotional offers and products and services which we think may interest you; 
    * for market research purposes - to better understand your needs;
    * to enable RANsquawk to manage customer service interactions with you; and 
    * where we have a legal right or duty to use or disclose your information (for example in relation to an investigation by a public authority or in a legal dispute). 
    * email marketing (if you have opted in) from RANsquawk as well as from our subsidiaries, affiliates, marketing partners, advertisers and other third parties 
  4. ## Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Similar Technologies

### What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small amount of data, which may include a unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. We assign a different cookie to each device that accesses our website. 

### Why does RANsquawk use cookies and similar tracking technology?

    * We use cookies to recognize your device and provide you with a personalized experience. 
    * We also use cookies to serve targeted ads from Google, Facebook, Bing, and other third-party vendors. 
    * Our third-party advertisers use cookies to track your prior visits to our websites and elsewhere on the Internet in order to serve you targeted ads. For more information about targeted or behavioral advertising, please visit <https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising>
    * We may also use web beacons, tracking technology and other automated tracking methods on our websites, in communications with you, and in our products and services, to measure performance and engagement. 

If you register with us, this cookie allows us to recognise you when you return to our website and provides you with access to your account information. If you save your information with or subscribe to us, we may also use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of our website. If you have not saved your information with or subscribed to us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our website in a manner that does not identify you. You can disable cookies at any time by using your browser options; however, if you turn off cookies, we will not be able to track your usage. In addition, we will not be able to recognise you as a registered user to allow you access to your account information. 

**Our websites work better with cookies enabled. Our cookies don't give us or anyone else access to your personal data.**

We strongly advise you to keep cookies enabled when you use RANsquawk's website. However, you can use your browser to delete and reject cookies. There are instructions on [how to delete cookies](http://www.aboutcookies.org/how-to-delete-cookies/)and [how to control cookies](http://www.aboutcookies.org/how-to-control-cookies/)on the About Cookies' website 

### Google Analytics

We want our website to be as user friendly as possible. To help us understand how well the website is working (and how we can improve it) we use third-party analytics tools such as Google Analytics. 

Analytics tools help us collect information about how people in general use our websites. For instance, it helps us monitor how many people visit each page, how long people stay on each page, which search engines people use to find our website and which links are clicked on. 

These cookies do not collect or store personal information about you. Analytics data cannot be used to identify you, or to tell us what you did on our website. It is completely anonymous. 

### Third Party Advertising Partners

We use third-party service providers to serve advertisements (banners or links) on our behalf across the Internet. 

These advertising service providers may collect non-identifiable information about your visits to our website, and your interactions with our products and services. Such non-identifiable information does not include your name, address, e-mail address or other personal information. The information is collected through the use of cookies and pixel tags (also known as action tags), which is industry-standard technology used by most major websites. 

In addition to the information about your visits to our website, our service providers may also use the information about your visits to other websites to target advertisements for products and services available from RANsquawk. 

You can opt out of all third party cookie advertising by visiting [http://optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/)

### Facebook Custom Audience Ads

We may display interest-based ads to you when you are using Facebook through a tool offered by Facebook called the Custom Audience Tool. This tool allows us to personalize our ads based on your browsing experience with us. We do not share any of your personal information with Facebook. The tool lets RANsquawk convert your email address to a unique number that Facebook uses to match to unique numbers Facebook generates from email addresses of its users. 

### Twitter Retargeting

RANsquawk may use, through its Website, the Twitter retargeting service to advertise on Twitter to previous visitors to our Website. Twitter retargeting is a retargeting and behavioural targeting service provided by Twitter. 

Twitter retargeting displays relevant advertisements to you based on pages of the RANsquawk Website that you have viewed by placing a cookie on your computer. This cookie does not identify you or give us access to your computer. The cookie allows us to show you relevant advertisements across the Twitter Network based on your previous browsing of the RANsquawk website. 

Any data that we collect will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy and Twitter’s retargeting privacy policy. 

You can opt out of all third party cookie advertising by visiting <http://optout.aboutads.info/>

  5. ## Email Marketing

We use MailChimp as our email marketing platform. The information you provide will be transferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)and [Terms.](https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/)

We allow you to elect to receive, or not receive, certain information from RANsquawk. RANsquawk adheres strictly to permission-based email policy. Except where mentioned above, RANsquawk will not send you unsolicited email information, commercial offers or advertisements. RANsquawk will not sell, rent, or loan our contact lists or our customer’s contact lists (including customer data) to any outside firms not involved in the provision of RANsquawk services, nor will RANsquawk use customer contact lists for our own marketing purposes. 

If you are opted in to receive marketing emails from us and wish to unsubscribe, you can do so by clicking on the Unsubscribe hyperlink at the bottom of the marketing email you receive or by sending an email to us at admin@ransquawk.com 

**Please note that opting-out of Marketing communications does not affect your receipt of business communications that are important to your interaction with RANsquawk, such as support/service communications, security updates or account management**

  6. ## Links to Other Websites

Our Site contains links to other websites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. Except as described above, we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of websites to which we link. Links from our web site to third parties or to other sites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information. 

  7. ## Sharing of Personal Information

We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this privacy policy. We share personal information with third-parties who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. These functions may include, for example, distributing emails, managing a database of customer information, providing fraud prevention, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments. We require our third party vendors to keep such information confidential and to only use the information for the purpose it was provided. We are not responsible for any additional information you provide directly to these parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them. 

We also disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply this privacy policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our customers´ rights, property or safety; to protect our customers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of our Site; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay. 

In addition, information about our customers, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of the business assets of the company. 

  8. ## Security

We have put into place reasonable security measures in an effort to protect personal information while it is under our control. 

  9. ## Policy Changes

We will periodically modify our Privacy Policy so that it remains relevant and current with changing technologies, applicable laws, evolving business practices, and the needs of our customers. Whenever we modify our privacy policy, we will post the revised policy here, with an updated revision date. If we make material changes to the policy or in how we will use your personal information, we will also notify you by other means, such as sending an email and/or posting a notice on our corporate website and/or social media pages prior to the changes taking effect. We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. We encourage you to periodically review the privacy statements for the products and services you use to learn how we are protecting your information. If you continue to use our website after notice of the change has been given, you will be deemed to have accepted such changes. 

  10. ## Access to your personal information

You can contact us to request a copy of your personal information or delete your information by emailing us at admin@ransquawk.com. We shall attend to your request on a confidential basis within thirty (30) days of the request being received. Any request for deletion will only be undertaken to the extent that it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements worldwide. 

Access of your personal information may be refused if: 

    * Providing access would pose a serious and imminent threat to life or health of a person; 
    * Providing access would create an unreasonable impact on the privacy of others; 
    * The request is frivolous and vexatious; or
    * Denial of access is authorised or required by law.
  11. ## How long do we keep your data?

We will not retain your data for longer than necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy. Different retention periods apply for different types of data, however the longest we will normally hold any personal data is 6 years. 

  12. ## Age restrictions

Our Services are available for purchase only for those over the age of 18. Our Services are not targeted to, intended to be consumed by or designed to entice individuals under the age of 18. If you know of or have reason to believe anyone under the age of 18 has provided us with any personal data, please contact us. 

  13. ## Your Comments or Concerns

We welcome your feedback. If you have any comments or concerns about this privacy policy or would like to contact us for any reason, you may reach a customer service representative via email at info@ransquawk.com or by phone at 020 3582 2778 

### Revised date May 2018
